<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Book Breakdowns</title>
    <link>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Book Breakdowns</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/beli3ver&#34;&gt;Malte Kiefer&lt;/a&gt; 2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Read a Book: The Classic Guide to Intelligent Reading</title>
      <link>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/how-to-read-a-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/how-to-read-a-book/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of the education, money, and effort around reading is spent on the first 6 grades. There isn&amp;rsquo;t much emphasis on improving skill level beyond that level. The average High Schooler doesn&amp;rsquo;t have the skills to understand and absorb complex ideas very efficiently. There isn&amp;rsquo;t much formal training to improve on this either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Money or Your Life: 9 Steps to Transforming Your Relationship with Money and Achieving Financial Independence: Revised and Updated for the 21st Century</title>
      <link>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/your-money-or-your-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/your-money-or-your-life/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This book explains the view that there is more to life than just working for more money so you can spend it. There are many studies that prove there there are much better goals to focus on that have a much larger impact on your happiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Work: Rules for Focused Success in a Distracted World</title>
      <link>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/deep-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/deep-work/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deep Work:&lt;/strong&gt; Professional activities performed in a state of distraction-free concentration that push your cognitive capabilities to their limit. These efforts create new value, improve your skill and are hard to replicate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peopleware: Productive Projects and Teams (3rd Edition)</title>
      <link>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/peopleware/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/peopleware/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The two authors of this book, Tom and Timothy made an observation one day that the biggest and most important problems they have as managers deal with people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So Good They Can&#39;t Ignore You: Why Skills Trump Passion in the Quest for Work You Love</title>
      <link>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/so-good-they-cant-ignore-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/so-good-they-cant-ignore-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In his book “So Good They Can’t Ignore You”, Cal recounts his quest to answer the question of why some people end up loving what they do, and why others fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Passionate Programmer: Creating a Remarkable Career in Software Development (Pragmatic Life)</title>
      <link>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/the-passionate-programmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bookbreakdowns.com/post/the-passionate-programmer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In his book, &amp;ldquo;The Passionate Programmer&amp;rdquo;, Chad Fowler explains how you likely aren&amp;rsquo;t putting enough thought into your career as a software developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>